[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 67 and height 48?",
      "correctAnswer": "1608.0",
      "options": [
        "1610.5",
        "1605.5",
        "1608.0",
        "1612.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 31 and height 50?",
      "correctAnswer": "775.0",
      "options": [
        "772.5",
        "775.0",
        "779.0",
        "777.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 29 and height 11?",
      "correctAnswer": "159.5",
      "options": [
        "157.0",
        "159.5",
        "162.0",
        "163.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 67 and height 21?",
      "correctAnswer": "703.5",
      "options": [
        "707.5",
        "703.5",
        "706.0",
        "701.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 1 and height 23?",
      "correctAnswer": "11.5",
      "options": [
        "15.5",
        "9.0",
        "11.5",
        "14.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 9 and height 34?",
      "correctAnswer": "153.0",
      "options": [
        "150.5",
        "157.0",
        "155.5",
        "153.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 67 and height 40?",
      "correctAnswer": "1340.0",
      "options": [
        "1342.5",
        "1340.0",
        "1344.0",
        "1337.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 30 and height 13?",
      "correctAnswer": "195.0",
      "options": [
        "195.0",
        "199.0",
        "192.5",
        "197.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 52 and height 55?",
      "correctAnswer": "1430.0",
      "options": [
        "1427.5",
        "1430.0",
        "1434.0",
        "1432.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 55 and height 52?",
      "correctAnswer": "1430.0",
      "options": [
        "1432.5",
        "1430.0",
        "1434.0",
        "1427.5"
      ]
    }
]